# Shamone Wilson

[63402@student.slzusd.org]

I have many life goals including things as in being healthy and fit. I also want to as educated on topics I enjoy like math and computer class. I want to go to MIT(Massachusetts Institute of Technology). I dont have alot of work experience, but I did do a small internship at State Farm for 2 weeks.

# **EDUCATION:**

Completed 1 year at San Lorenzo High School Graduation Date: [June 13, 2021]

# **EXPERIENCE:**

File Manager, State Farm in San Diego
I assisted a employee at State Farm will the load of files he
consistantly recieved

July 12-26, 2014

## **HONORS and AWARDS:**

Math Magician [Feaster Charter School]

[May 13, 2011]

I got good grades in elementry for my math classes so after I graduated 1st grade, I recieved an award along wit my honor roll called Math Magician.

Perfect Attendance[Elementry, Middle, and High School]

[Unidentifiable]

I always tried my best to go to school every day.

[Title][Organization]

[Date Received]

[Description]

### SKILLS:

I am great at staying calm in crazy situations and I can calm down many stressed people. I am pretty good at math aswell. My teamwork skills are pretty exceptional aswell. I enjoy reading and playing video games. It is childish of me, but I enjoy playing with LEGOs at times. I'm interested in computors and curtain health topics. Biology was a fun class for me. So was computer science class.

# Marina Rodriguez

marina.rodriguez@ousd.us

A young, responsible, and passionate student who is hoping to work with food and people in the future.

## **EDUCATION:**

Completed 1 year at Madison Park Academy High School

Graduation Date: 06/09/2021 Pathway Focus: Digital Design

### **EXPERIENCE:**

Babysitter - Oakland, CA

June, 2014 - Present

January, 2018

Babysitter for local families after school and on weekends. Provides meals for children and tutors students in 1st - 8th grade content.

Food Pantry Volunteer - Church of Light: Oakland, CA August, 2014 - June, 2017 Helps to cook full meals for the homeless in Oakland. Serves 200 people per meal provided.

Academic Tutor - Madison Park Academy May, 2014 - September, 2016 Provides academic support for 10 elementary students in Math and Science after school for 2 hours a day.

### **HONORS and AWARDS:**

Honor Roll - Madison Park Academy
Received an academic award for earning a GPA above a 3.5

Most Valuable Player - Madison Park Academy December, 2017 Received a trophy of recognition for my role as a forward on MPA's varsity soccer team.

2nd Place in Portrait Contest - Oakland Museum of California June, 2016 Received a ribbon for placing 2nd in the youth division of the Oakland Museum's annual portrait contest.

### SKILLS:

Cooking: baking. Art: Photoshop, painting, and drawing. Hobbies: Soccer and slam poetry.